{
  "crackerQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "Who tries to stop Christmas from coming, by stealing all things of Christmas from “the Who’s”?",
      "answer": "The Grinch",
      "options": ["The Grinch", "Scrooge", "Donald Trump", "The Dalai Lama"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first name of Scrooge, the principal character of the novel, A Christmas Carol?",
      "answer": "Ebenezer",
      "options": ["Gerald", "Ebenezer", "The", "Huge"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the other reindeer pick on Rudolph?",
      "answer": "His red nose",
      "options": [
        "He smelled",
        "His red nose",
        "His political opinions",
        "He didn't believe in Santa"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What name is given to small sausages wrapped in bacon, a staple at a British Christmas dinner?",
      "answer": "Pigs in blankets",
      "options": [
        "Baconages",
        "Double the pig, twice the fun",
        "Pigs in blankets",
        "Pig squared"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does feliz navidad translate to in English?",
      "answer": "Happy Christmas",
      "options": [
        "Happy Easter",
        "Happy Christmas",
        "Happy Happy",
        "I feel for my dad in the navy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who sang the hit single - All I want for Christmas is you",
      "answer": "Mariah Carey",
      "options": [
        "Mariah dont Care",
        "Mariah cares very much",
        "Mariah Carey",
        "Mariah carries the bags"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Canada, The U.K., and most other Commonwealth countries officially celebrate the day after Christmas as what holiday?",
      "answer": "Boxing Day",
      "options": ["Boxing day", "Christmas Morrow", "Easter", "Thanksgiving"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The legend of Santa Claus is associated with which saint?",
      "answer": "Saint Nicholas",
      "options": [
        "Southampton FC",
        "Saint Nicholas",
        "Joan of Arc",
        "Saint Santa"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company made the concept of Santa Claus popular worldwide?",
      "answer": "Coca Cola",
      "options": ["Coca Cola", "Station 10", ""]
    },
    {
      "question": "According to the Holy Bible, Jesus Christ was born in a?",
      "answer": "Stable",
      "options": ["Hiltons", "Van", "Stable", "Hurry"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is NOT one of the eight original reindeer?",
      "answer": "Dave",
      "options": ["Dasher", "Dave", "Dancer", "Donner"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these was a gift given to Jesus from one of the Three Wise Men?",
      "answer": "Gold",
      "options": ["PS5", "A brand new car", "Gold", "Apple Watch"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song begins with “Joy to the World, the Saviour reigns!”?",
      "answer": "Joy to the World",
      "options": [
        "Joy to the World",
        "Hit me baby one more time",
        "Backstreets back",
        "Jingle Bells"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "In Elf, what is considered the first rule of The Code of Elves?",
      "answer": "Treat every day like it's Christmas",
      "options": [
        "We do NOT talk about elf club!",
        "Treat every day like it's Christmas",
        "Never eat yellow snow",
        "Nothing in this world is free"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What film features the line \"I made my family disappear.\"",
      "answer": "Home Alone",
      "options": ["Harry Potter", "Die Hard", "Home Alone", "Star Wars"]
    }
  ],
  "jokes": [
    {
      "question": "What does Santa suffer from if he gets stuck in a chimney?",
      "answer": "Claustrophobia!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of motorbike does Santa ride?",
      "answer": "A Holly Davidson!"
    },
    { "question": "Who delivers presents to cats?", "answer": "Santa Paws!" },
    {
      "question": "What did the sea Say to Santa?",
      "answer": "Nothing! It just waved!"
    },
    {
      "question": "How you can tell that Santa is real?",
      "answer": "You can always sense his presents!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you get if you cross Santa with a duck?",
      "answer": "A Christmas Quacker!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why does Santa go down the chimney on Christmas Eve?",
      "answer": "Because it 'soots' him!"
    },
    { "question": "What's Santa's favorite type of music?", "answer": "Wrap!" },
    {
      "question": "What do Santa's little helpers learn at school?",
      "answer": "The elf-abet!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did Santa say to the smoker?",
      "answer": "Please don't smoke, it's bad for my elf!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a man who claps at Christmas?",
      "answer": "Santapplause!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of cars do elves like to drive?",
      "answer": "A Toy-ota!"
    },
    { "question": "What do elves post on Social Media?", "answer": "Elf-ies!" },
    {
      "question": "What do you call Rudolph with lots of snow in his ears?",
      "answer": "Anything you want, he can't hear you!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Santa clean his hands with?",
      "answer": "Santatizer!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the turkey join the band?",
      "answer": "Because it had the drumsticks!"
    },
    { "question": "How does a snowman get to work?", "answer": "By icicle!" },
    {
      "question": "What did one snowman say to the other?",
      "answer": "I couldn't hear them, so I have snow-idea!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do snowmen like to do on the weekend?",
      "answer": "Chill!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a snowman who has a holiday in the tropics?",
      "answer": "A puddle!"
    }
  ]
}
